{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: his", "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive pronoun.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["This", "his", "awakened", "on"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: opened", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["opened", "the", "soon", "his"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: pass", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "Just then the little mouse happened to pass by . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["pass", "the", "happened", "mouse"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "And who knows , I may be able to do you a good turn one of these days ! '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["And", "you", "able", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: shall", "question": "In the following sentence identify Model.", "comprehension": "I shall never repeat it and I shall never forget your kindness . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["I", "never", "shall", "your"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: plight", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "On seeing the lion 's plight , he ran up to him and gnawed away the ropes that bound him , the king of the jungle . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["On", "ropes", "him", "plight"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: help", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "said the little mouse , very happy to help the lion . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["lion", "help", "to", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: his", "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "help", "him", "his"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: And", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "And who knows , I may be able to do you a good turn one of these days ! '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["one", "days", "may", "And"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: Just", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Just then the little mouse happened to pass by . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["happened", "mouse", "by", "Just"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: by", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Just then the little mouse happened to pass by . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["pass", "mouse", "Just", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: After", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "After", "went", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: huge", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["his", "him", "to", "huge"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "said the little mouse , very happy to help the lion . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["mouse", "very", "the", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: you", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "And who knows , I may be able to do you a good turn one of these days ! '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["you", "turn", "knows", "may"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: take", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["take", "to", "a", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify WH-determiner.", "comprehension": "On seeing the lion 's plight , he ran up to him and gnawed away the ropes that bound him , the king of the jungle . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "On", "him", "he"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["of", "a", "began", "down"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: captured", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["captured", "to", "tied", "Sometime"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["went", "a", "zoo", "in"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: king", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "On seeing the lion 's plight , he ran up to him and gnawed away the ropes that bound him , the king of the jungle . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "gnawed", "he", "king"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["a", "to", "him", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "Just then the little mouse happened to pass by . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["pass", "then", "by", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["little", "of", "down", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: asleep", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["him", "asleep", "a", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: this", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "`` Forgive me this time . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["this", "me", "Forgive", "time"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["few", "to", "him", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: began", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["began", "running", "of", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: paw", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["paw", "tickled", "that", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["captured", "few", "a", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: repeat", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "I shall never repeat it and I shall never forget your kindness . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["shall", "your", "and", "repeat"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: Was", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "`` Was I not right ? '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["not", "right", "Was", "I"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "said the little mouse , very happy to help the lion . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "help", "lion", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["go", "to", "that", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "On seeing the lion 's plight , he ran up to him and gnawed away the ropes that bound him , the king of the jungle . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["away", "lion", "the", "bound"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: little", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "cried the little mouse . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "cried", "mouse", "little"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["the", "his", "opened", "awakened"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: little", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "said the little mouse , very happy to help the lion . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["little", "the", "the", "very"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: it", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "I shall never repeat it and I shall never forget your kindness . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["it", "and", "never", "forget"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: search", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["search", "of", "After", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: never", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "I shall never repeat it and I shall never forget your kindness . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["never", "it", "your", "I"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: down", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["lion", "a", "down", "began"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: go", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["idea", "and", "being", "go"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: time", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "`` Forgive me this time . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["time", "this", "Forgive", "me"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: so", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["being", "so", "him", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: be", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "And who knows , I may be able to do you a good turn one of these days ! '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["you", "And", "days", "be"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: mouse", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "cried the little mouse . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["little", "the", "mouse", "cried"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: On", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "On seeing the lion 's plight , he ran up to him and gnawed away the ropes that bound him , the king of the jungle . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["ran", "ropes", "to", "On"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: these", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "And who knows , I may be able to do you a good turn one of these days ! '' ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["these", "to", "you", "And"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "the", "his", "on"]}], "success": 1}